<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>gristlepod store updates</title>
    <link>https://gristlepod.github.io/</link>
    <description>gristlepod is an illustrator and developer residing in the github hosting space. this feed records sitely updates, store news, and the like.</description>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <webMaster>0ekekddddd@protonmail.com</webMaster>
    <copyright>sam @ gristlepod</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>2025.03.04 // Coming Together.  $10 Sketch Terms Updated, Mini Prints Relocated.</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 Mar 2025 15:06:53 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>I've been getting a lot more sketch requests lately and decided to update its terms to neighbor my plans for the shop's future meaning I won't be doing colored sketches anymore. I'm gonna be taking my art in-person to conventions local to me and will post a line-up when my applications are reviewed. I'm pretty excited as I've been handling the table display massproducing stock as well as designing both fanmerch and personal merch. I encourage those new to the website to subscribe to my RSS if you're in the US and interested in Identity V merch.</p>
<p>I'm briefly closing commissions while I focus on the new rove into vending, but they'll be back when I'm not as busy.</p>
<p>Following the last update the Ko-fi store is back online and I've sorted things out with moderation. Shop was looking a little chaotic so I've relocated all prints into one list.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.21 //  Cosplay Prop Commissions @ Etsy</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 10:14:42 -0600</pubDate>
      <link>https://www.etsy.com/shop/PrintedByAPod</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>I've opened a storepage over at Etsy to pay off some bills. I've been doing propwork for a few years now (both foamsmithing and recently 3d printing), and I've gotten good feedback about my modeling work prior. If any Identity V fans are missing a Norton compass or need a kukri blade to complete their Luchino or Naib cosplay, visit my page @ <a href="https://www.etsy.com/shop/PrintedByAPod">PrintedByAPod</a>. More designs coming soon.</p><p>On another note, the Ko-fi page may be down due to some misunderstandings with the moderation over on the site. I already submitted an appeal, but it shouldn't break anyone's ability to commission me. As always, my contact is 0ekekddddd@protonmail.com for slots. Thanks for reading.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.06 // Preorders for Dot Ship Acrylic Charms, YCH slots</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 16:54:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<a href="https://ko-fi.com/s/0d3f47d398">Preorders on Ko-fi </a>for (my first) and new series of acrylic charms are now live. I've also set up a <a href="https://ko-fi.com/c/79205d3bc7">YCH commission service</a> based on these designs.<p align="center"><img style="max-width: 400px; width: 40%" src="https://gristlepod.github.io/rss/thumbnails/dotych_debut.png"></p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025.02.05 // Market Blog: Start!</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 5 Feb 2025 16:54:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>I've hoisted the beams for a new blog in regards to future product announcements as well as the convenience of my followers. Of course, for the luddites, I've tailored an RSS feed completely for you. By subscribing to this feed, you may get early updates about my newest merch designs, when the Ko-fi store page has a new item, or when I open preorders.</p>
<p>Thanks for checking in.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>