<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <generator>RSS Builder by B!Soft</generator>
    <title>gristlepod site updates</title>
    <link>https://gristlepod.github.io/</link>
    <description>gristlepod is an illustrator and developer residing in the github hosting space. this feed records sitely updates and personal logging.</description>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <webMaster>0ekekddddd@protonmail.com</webMaster>
    <copyright>sam @ gristlepod</copyright>
    <item>
      <title>2025.2.06 // "Refléter Op. 6", RSS feed applied</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 6 Feb 2025 18:35:57 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>several graphic changes were applied to the site and some directories were recategorized for the following update. i've set up two rss feeds respectively for my personal blog and store. the landing page will now display the newest posts of both feeds. </p>
<p>posted&nbsp;an&nbsp;identity v&nbsp;fanfiction "Refléter Op. 6" that i've written some time ago in personal log &gt; fanfiction</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.12.22 // spreadsheet redeco</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 18:31:04 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>touched up the music page and sorted my spreadsheet archive to be used globally rather than page by page. cleaned up luchino's shrine.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.11.03 // 0ekekddddd ==&gt; gristlepod@github</title>
      <pubDate>Sun, 3 Nov 2024 18:25:10 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>working towards a more streamlined brand, and having to spell "0ekekddddd" out loud at meetups gets embarrassing. url change enacted. also, i made a <a href="https://bsky.app/profile/gristlepod.bsky.social" target=_blank>bluesky</a>.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.09.06 // church of luchino</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 6 Sep 2024 18:25:09 -0600</pubDate>
      <link>/luchino_shrine/</link>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>Edited on 2025.2.6. Date when the Church of Luchino was posted.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024.08.24 // general website-itry</title>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 18:17:49 -0600</pubDate>
      <description><![CDATA[<p>site changes are officially being recorded... i might have waited too long to do this ever since the host switch. a brand new sitewide layout graphic has been applied for the special occasion, but i'll keep using the old one for the blog. regarding ko-fi i've come across issues with overseas sales, so i'll issue a list of countries i can't ship to internationally in the upcoming commission TOS.</p>]]></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>